Off the stage through Mary.
[cheering]
>> Namaskar.
>> Hi guys.
>> Yeah. Now, now the mic is working.
Correct.
Um really excited to see you all here.
>> Before I start, uh can you guys raise
your hands if you already know me?
Okay, that's [laughter]
>> that's a lot of people. Maybe people who
don't know me should raise their hands.
Okay, that's that's a significant amount
also. So, let me start with a small
introduction. I'm an Indian YouTuber and
educator with more than 30 million
followers on YouTube and 16 million on
Instagram. I have a channel on education
and explanatory videos. I also have my
online course academy and just to give
you an idea of the kind of videos I make
on my channel. It's basically all kinds
of topic. It's any kind of educational
topic. Science, history, current
affairs, news, politics. I make videos
on all these things. But the story I
want to tell you today is my attempt at
doing something different. Most of the
people present here are creators. Some
of you have an audience. Some of you are
building an audience and some of you
dream of doing uh more than content one
day because at one point every creator
asks themsself, "How do I turn this into
something real? Not just views, not just
brand deals, but something you own like
a product, a company, or a system that
works even when you're offline."
Well, this is exactly what I tried to
do.
Four months ago, I launched my first
startup
and I learned very quickly that building
a business is very different from
building an audience. This was the video
where I launched the startup. A bit of a
clickbait title, but uh just to give you
an idea what my business was about.
It was a simple idea. You know nowadays
we have so many different AI models from
Chad GPT, Gemini, Claude, uh,
Perplexity, Grock and all of these
different uh, AI models. One day Gemini
is the best model. The next month Chad
GPT comes with a better model. The next
day uh, Claude comes with a better
model. So my idea was why not have one
place where you can get all these
premium AI models in one chat at a price
cheaper than one subscription. And this
is where the idea for AI Fiesta was
born. The concept is very simple. The
business model makes sense like you pay
$20 a month for Chad GPT plus
subscription. You pay $20 a month for
Google Gemini. Uh $20 a month for CL.
$30 a month for Grock. So only if you
add all these top five or six
subscriptions you end up get paying $110
a month. This was a problem that I was
also facing. And then we decided why not
have all these premium AI models in one
app for just $12 a month which is
cheaper than any of these one
subscriptions. And this is what we
built. So this is how the interface
looks like. You ask a prompt and you can
have all these different AIS. There can
be up to 10 different AIs ask answering
your one question all at the same time
simultaneously. So you can always choose
the best answer for every question that
you have and you can compare the
answers.
Before I move on to tell you what
happened after we launched, there is
something I want to tell you if you are
thinking of you know starting your own
business and this is something which
I've always believed in. If you are
starting your own company, you need to
find a real problem and then find a
solution for that problem. Because what
most people do is they think that oh I
have this idea. I want to build a
business. I want to build this company.
Let me build it on this idea. But this
is the wrong way of doing it. And this I
believe is more like you think of a
solution and then your solution is
trying to find a problem. But instead it
should be the other way around.
encounter a problem and then look for a
solution for that. And this is how I
came up with this idea because this is
something that I was facing in my
personal life also that you know all
these different AI subscriptions better
to have one app and this is when I built
it. So I launched this 4 months ago and
then this happened.
The whole internet was flooded with
videos like this calling my new startup
a scam. Uh some were calling it a scam.
Some said it was misleading. Some said
it was a crash cash grab. There was hate
coming from all sides trolling
everywhere.
And
you might ask why that happened. Of
course there was many reasons for it.
Some of it was our mistakes. Some of it
was misunderstandings. For example, uh
one of our mistakes was we did not
clarify exactly what the token limits
were and people thought the token limits
were very less for example. Another
reason was a communication gap. Um one
one of the biggest reasons was that when
people went to purchase the product
because of the launch video there was a
huge traffic coming into this app and at
one point there was like thousands and
thousands of people trying to buy the
subscription of this app and the payment
system crashed. People paid for the app
but they did not get access to it. So of
course you know how how would you react
if that happens? You would think that
there's some serious bug here. But what
happens is that when people don't
understand something, they don't give
you the benefit of the doubt. Especially
when you're at this level, they they
instead believe it is your intent to do
that. So when the payment crashed,
people paid for it, did not get the
service, they assumed that this is how I
intended it to be. And that's how they
assumed it was a scam. And then what
happened after this? So many people not
getting what they expect, not getting
the service. All of them would in mass
send emails to our customer support. So
there was thousands and thousands of
email coming in our customer support
inbox. All of the people saying, "I paid
for this. I did not get it. Give me a
refund. This is a scam." Blah blah blah.
So within 2 days, we had at least 5,000
emails in our customer support. And to
make things worse, what happened after
this is this chat GPT right after we
launch our service, they decide, okay,
we're going to launch a cheaper
subscription plan, but just for India.
Initially, it was $20 a month. We
decided to say that okay, we'll give you
all these AIS at $12 a month. And then
Chad GPT 2 days later comes and says
actually just for India we'll launch an
even cheaper subscription plan at only
$5 a month. [laughter]
[snorts]
And that wasn't it. In a few weeks
Chad GPT says actually not even $5 have
it for free
for the next 12 months. They're like
we'll give it to you for free this Chad
GPT go subscription. So it's a it's a
lot of headache. 10 years of content
creation had not prepared me for this.
There's problems from all sides. There
there's payment issues. People are not
happy. People are calling it a scam. And
on top of that there's like the
competition is giving away their AI
models for free. The question is how
would you deal with all this? And before
I tell you how did we deal with all
this, I want to tell you two things I
learned in the process.
The first thing is that I cannot
emphasize how important it is to have
the right person to work with. My
co-founder and the business side of
things is handled by my partner who's
standing over there and
and um all I can say is if I did not
have him, I would have no idea how to
handle this. It's so important to find
someone who is in sync with you and
supporting you in the bad times and the
good times. It's going to be, by the
way, it's going to be really hard to
make a business alone. If you're
thinking that you're a creator and
you're going to build a company all
alone by yourself, it's it's basically
impossible because there's so many
day-to-day affairs of making a company.
There's like the customer support,
there's the product development, there's
um HR, so many things you need to
manage. So it's almost impossible to do
it alone but with the wrong person it
could be a complete disaster. So that's
why this is very important finding the
right person to work with someone who
can be handle the business side of
things while you as a creator is
managing mostly the marketing side. Now
the second thing I learned is that
something will always go wrong. No
matter how prepared you are something
will always go wrong. And you might
think listening to the story that maybe
we were underprepared to handle all
this, but trust me, from our end, we had
a checklist. We had double checked that
checklist. We had triple checked all our
things. It's just that there's so many
different things that can go wrong that
something will eventually go wrong. It's
it's it's a bit like trying to make your
first YouTube video. You always try to
think it's my first video, it should be
perfect, but it will never be perfect
because it's your first attempt at doing
that. So just like in your first YouTube
video that something will go wrong. The
same thing is true for your business or
your company that on day one something
will go wrong. So it's better to be
mentally prepared that something will go
wrong and I will handle it. So the more
prepared you are, the more quickly you
you will accept the failures and move
on. Now the question is coming back to
the story, how did we handle all this?
Well, the first thing we did is
obviously acknowledge our mistakes. We
tried to solve all these payment issues
as quickly as we could. But again, there
was like 5,000 emails in the customer
support inbox. We had to get creative.
What we did was we hired a temporary
team of 10 plus people just to answer
the customer queries. And these 10 15
people they sat down day and night for
the whole weekend answering all the
emails one by one until over the weekend
we we were done with answering all the
queries. At the same time all the server
crashes that happened we fixed that. The
product uh development team helped to
improve it as quickly as they could. We
also built an AI chatbot to answer our
customer queries. So after the first
weekend uh up to 40% of the customer
queries were solved by our AI chatbot
which reduced the workload a lot but
most importantly we communicated
everything to people as transparently as
possible.
This was the second video I made after
that first attempt and immediately we
increased our token limits by 10 times.
We added new features what people
expected out of us. The product
development team was working day and
night and within one week we had these
changes. I made another video one month
later where I explained the whole story
in a more detailed way. I I explained
why things went wrong, how they did how
how they went wrong and what we did to
manage them and how we trying to work on
this. And the conclusion here is that
it's it's so important to be transparent
and authentic to your audience because
as a creator, this is all you have.
Trust is your most valuable asset as a
creator.
And this is what I kept believing in and
I learned over this process. And for the
next two months, I was transparent about
everything with my audience. We told
them every feature update we had uh we
were making videos on that updating
everything. We course corrected,
admitted mistakes and moved on quickly.
And because of that slowly the reviews
started improving and I think after 2
months you could see positive reviews
coming on in the trust pilot. The
customer support improved. People were
very happy with this
and we even did like customer calls. So
this was uh my idea that every week we'd
randomly pick 20 customers and go on a
call with them to understand their
desires, their pain points and their
needs. And you might think that you know
as a creator with 30 million subscribers
and tens of thousands of pe of people
are using the app. What difference does
it make if if there's like I'm talking
with 20 people but this is all the
difference it makes. I I understood the
needs of customers. I I understood what
they wanted and this I could only
understand by talking to them on these
small calls
and then I also understood that customer
satisfaction should be your number one
goal as a company. You're not building a
company for yourself. You're building it
for the customer. And I truly believe
that if you work on giving the best
product, the best experience for your
first thousand customers, they will like
the product and they will become your
marketing channels for the future. So we
kept doing this for months. We kept
learning and heads down building. We
kept providing new features. To give you
an example, I think in the last couple
of months, we also added a consensus
feature. Uh the problem many people
said, you know, there's 10 different
AIS, 10 different responses. It's so
hard to read through all the 10
different responses. Why not have an AI
model? Take those 10 responses and give
us the consensus of that. Like what's
the summary? If if eight of those 10
models agree on something, I want to
know which of these models agree, which
two models disagree, and what do they
disagree about? So, this feature does
exactly that. We also added a super
fiesta mode where um in a single chat,
you can switch between different AI
models. When you send your question,
your prompt to the AI, our proprietary
algorithm decides which AI this question
should go to. So in a single chat you
can switch between Gemini claude chat
GPT and always have the best answer. So
so we built a light mode we added
avatars and um because of all this
because of whatever we worked on today
AFiesta has more than 70,000 paid
subscribers.
We did
we did more than 2 million 2.5 million
in revenue since 4 months of launching.
And today we provide more than 10
different AI providers, 35 different AI
models in one place to get you the best
answer always.
And what's next is we are building even
more. We are adding a dedicated study
mode. We are going to add a dedicated
image mode so all the different top
image generation models can be at one
place. But more importantly than this,
we are thinking of expanding
internationally now because this product
was only available to the Indian
audience till now. So for that, what
better opportunity than the 1 billion
summit. If any of you is interested in
partnering with us, please scan this QR
code and you can sign up as an
affiliate. We offer 25% lifetime
commissions. Most of the other companies
they offer like one, two months or three
months commissions. But we believe that
if you bring a customer, you will earn
25% of that as long as they stay a part
of the service as a as a part of the
subscription.
And of course, you will also get free AI
fiesta subscription if you join on. And
one last thing I'd like to say is if any
of you is interested in a deeper
collaboration with us to expand to
international markets, you can reach out
to me or you can also write an email to
support aifiesta.ai
supportiesta.ai.
And one last advice, if you're thinking
of starting a company, believe in
yourself. Start now, adapt as you go
along. And I truly believe you can do
it. Thank you.